https://circlesanctuary.org/index.php/organization/privacy-policy

HomeOur Work
Circle CemeteryCircle Sanctuary Network PodcastsCircle Sanctuary Network Podcasts ArchiveCircle Craft Podcast ArchiveHealingInterfaith WorkLady Liberty LeagueMilitary MinistriesNature PreserveYoung Professionals NetworkEventsEvent CalendarFull Moon CircleSanctuary DaysPagan Spirit GatheringSacred Fire CirclesCommunity
MembershipOur CommunityInclusiveness PolicyIn MemoriamAbout Us
About CircleAbout Rev. Selena FoxMinistersBoard of DirectorsAnnual ReportsConstitutionBylawsHistoryTeachings
About PaganismCelebrating the SeasonsPlanning Pagan WeddingsMinistry Training ProgramSupport Us
DonateOnline StoreMembershipContact Us
Contact UsEmail ListsSocial NetworkingVisiting UsDONATE
HomeOur WorkCircle CemeteryCircle Sanctuary Network PodcastsCircle Sanctuary Network Podcasts ArchiveCircle Craft Podcast ArchiveHealingInterfaith WorkLady Liberty LeagueMilitary MinistriesNature PreserveYoung Professionals NetworkEventsEvent CalendarFull Moon CircleSanctuary DaysPagan Spirit GatheringSacred Fire CirclesCommunityMembershipOur CommunityInclusiveness PolicyIn MemoriamAbout UsAbout CircleAbout Rev. Selena FoxMinistersBoard of DirectorsAnnual ReportsConstitutionBylawsHistoryTeachingsAbout PaganismCelebrating the SeasonsPlanning Pagan WeddingsMinistry Training ProgramSupport UsDonateOnline StoreMembershipContact UsContact UsEmail ListsSocial NetworkingVisiting UsDONATE
Privacy Policy
Since its founding in 1974, Circle Sanctuary, also known as Circle, has valued and safeguarded the privacy of all those who have participated in the networking and other services we provide. Whether received by postal mail, face-to-face, fax, and/or electronically, our policy is that we do not sell, trade, or pass on the names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and other contact information to others without permission.
Our Commitment to Online Security Physical, electronic and managerial procedures have been employed to safeguard the security and integrity of personal information. Circle Sanctuary encrypts billing and other personal information wherever we request it. All Circle Sanctuary staff with access to personal information are also bound to adhere to this policy as part of their work with Circle Sanctuary.
Personal Information that Circle Sanctuary May Collect Online
Circle Sanctuary collects personal information online including names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone numbers and billing information.
How Circle Sanctuary Uses Personal Information Collected Online
Unless you otherwise consent, we will use your personal information only for the purpose for which it is submitted, such as to reply to your emails, process event registrations and store orders, and place you on email lists pertinent to your connections with us.  We will also use such information to provide operational notices, in program record-keeping and to conduct internal research.  At any time, you can add or remove your name from a Circle Sanctuary email list by contacting the webmaster.
How Your Information May Be Shared
Circle Sanctuary may share your information with our paid and volunteer staff members in the course of conducting regular business, such as running a Circle Sanctuary festival or handling a Lady Liberty League inquiry. We never sell, barter, or rent your personal information.
Circle Sanctuary remains steadfast in our commitment to safeguard privacy on-line and in other communications, and continues its long-standing commitment to working for a peaceful, healthy world and to prevent harm.  Should a special circumstance arise such as a need to cooperate with a government agency in the stopping of a fraudulent or other harmful practice, or to fulfill a subpoena or other legal obligation, Circle Sanctuary may choose to release data pertinent to the situation.
Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate
If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file, please contact the Circle Office. Let us also know what led to your submission of personal information so we may efficiently locate your information.
Computer Tracking and Cookies To provide deeper analytical data on how the circlesanctuary.org site is used, we partner with Google Analytics to provide aggregate statistics on usage patterns.  For more information on Google Analytics' privacy policy, please click here.
Problems or Complaints with Circle Sanctuary Privacy Policy If you have a complaint about Circle Sanctuary's compliance with this privacy policy, please contact Rev. Bob Paxton, the Circle webmaster and Board Secretary.
back to top
© 2020 Circle Sanctuary, Inc.
All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Desktop Version
You are now being logged in using your Facebook credentials
